 [
    {
      "question": "Which club won the Champions League Final in 1997?",
      "choice1": "FC Barcelona",
      "choice2": "Juventus F.C.",
      "choice3": "Borussia Dortmund",
      "choice4": "FC Bayern Munich",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who scored the winnning goal of the Champions League final in 2006?",
      "choice1": "Samuel Eto'o",
      "choice2": "Juliano Balleti",
      "choice3": "Andres iniesta",
      "choice4": "Thierry Henry",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which country was the winner of 1992 European Cup Final?",
      "choice1": "Germany",
      "choice2": "France",
      "choice3": "England",
      "choice4": "Denmark",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which club was the runner-up at 1991 European Cup Final?",
      "choice1": "Marseille FC",
      "choice2": "Real Madrid CF",
      "choice3": "Eintracht Frankfurt",
      "choice4": "FC Bayern Munich ",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the score between Chelsea-Barcelona in the second-leg of Champions League Semi-Finals in 2009?",
      "choice1": "Chelsea 0 - 0 Barcelona",
      "choice2": "Chelsea 0 - 1 Barcelona ",
      "choice3": "Chelsea 2 - 1 Barcelona ",
      "choice4": "Chelsea 1 - 1 Barcelona",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team won the 2015-2016 English Premier League?",
      "choice1": "Liverpool",
      "choice2": "Chelsea",
      "choice3": "Manchester City",
      "choice4": "Leicester City",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which club was the runner-up at 2010 Champions League Final?",
      "choice1": "FC Barcelona",
      "choice2": "FC Bayern Munich",
      "choice3": "Inter Milan",
      "choice4": "Real Madrid CF",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which British football stadium was the first to host a European Cup Final?",
      "choice1": "Anfield",
      "choice2": "Old Traford",
      "choice3": "Wembley",
      "choice4": "Hampden Park",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the score between Liverpool and A.C Milan in the first half in 2005 UCL final?",
      "choice1": "Milan 2 - 0 Liverpool",
      "choice2": "Milan 0 - 1 Liverpool",
      "choice3": "Milan 3 - 0 Liverpool",
      "choice4": "Milan 1 - 2 Liverpool",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who has the most Champions League goals ever?",
      "choice1": "Lionel Messi",
      "choice2": "Kaka",
      "choice3": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "choice4": "Luiz Suarez",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which football team won the la liga in 2013-2014 season?",
      "choice1": "Real Madrid CF",
      "choice2": "sevilla FC",
      "choice3": "Atletico Madrid",
      "choice4": "FC Barcelona",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who missed the first penalty for Chelsea in the finals of the UCL in 2007-2008 season ",
      "choice1": "Didier Drogba",
      "choice2": "John Terry",
      "choice3": "Nicolas Anelka",
      "choice4": "Malouda",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Greek club did Ajax beat to win their first European Cup?",
      "choice1": "Panathinaikos F.C.",
      "choice2": "AEK Athenes F.C.",
      "choice3": "Olympiacos F.C.",
      "choice4": "Aris F.C.",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Who was the coach of FC Barcelona in 1995-1996 season?",
    "choice1": "Ronald Koeman",
    "choice2": "Louis Van Gaal",
    "choice3": "Johan Cruyff",
    "choice4": "Carles Rexach",
    "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first football player to move from FC barcelona to Real Madrid CF?",
      "choice1": "Ronaldo jr",
      "choice2": "Luis Figo",
      "choice3": "Luis Enrique",
      "choice4": "Alfonso Albeniz",
      "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "Which season was Real Madrid's first Champions League title",
        "choice1": "1959-1960",
        "choice2": "1965-1966",
        "choice3": "1955-1956",
        "choice4": "1991-1992",
        "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "question": "In which football club was Cristiano Ronaldo first raised",
          "choice1": "Manchester United",
          "choice2": "Sporting CP",
          "choice3": "SL Benfica",
          "choice4": "FC Porto",
          "answer": 2
          }
  ]